Finding aid of the Herbert Hutchinson Brimley Photograph Collection, 1880-1977 PHC.42
State Archives of North Carolina
- Scenic Western NC, PhC.42.WesternNC; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mt. Pisgah, Henderson Co., NC, 1921. (18n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F14-19; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mt. Pisgah, Henderson Co., NC, 1921. (18n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F14-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mt. Pisgah, Henderson Co., NC, 1921. (18n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F14-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mt. Pisgah, Henderson Co., NC, 1921. (18n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F14-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mt. Pisgah, Henderson Co., NC, 1921. (18n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F14-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mt. Pisgah, Henderson Co., NC, 1921. (18n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F14-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mt. Pisgah, Henderson Co., NC, 1921. (18n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F14-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mt. Pisgah, Henderson Co., NC, 1921. (18n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F14-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mt. Pisgah, Henderson Co., NC, 1921. (18n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F14-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Near Round Knob, McDowell Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain farm, McDowell Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F16; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Stroups Trestle, McDowell Co., NC, ca. 1890., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F17; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Country Road, Buncombe Co., NC, ca. 1890., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F18; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Pasture, Buncombe Co., NC, ca. 1890., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F19; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain streams and mill, ca. 1900. (n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - The Swannanoa River, Buncombe Co., NC, ca. 1890., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F20; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Murphy Division, Southern Railway, Haywood County, NC, ca. 1890., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F21; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Pigeon River, Haywood County, NC, ca. 1890., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F22; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Round Knob, McDowell Co., NC, ca. 1890., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F23; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Southern Railroad winding around Round Knob, McDowell Co., NC, ca. 1890., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F24; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Jefferson and Negro Mountain, Ashe Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F25; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Wild Cat Rock, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F26; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Farm lands in the North fork of New River, Ashe Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F27; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Omakaluka Cascades near Highlands, NC/Caesar's Head, NC/SC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F28; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Chimney Rock and Falls, Rutherford Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F29; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Scenic valley in Henderson Co., NC, ca. 1900. (n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Near Chimney Rock, Rutherford Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F30; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Cox Farm, Rutherford Co., NC, ca. 1890., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F31; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Valley Farm, Rutherford Co., NC, ca. 1890., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F32; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Murphy Division, Southern Railway, Jackson Co., NC, ca. 1890., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F33; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Southern Railway, McDowell Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F34; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain peaks above clouds, Buncombe Co., NC, 1890; Railroad from Round Knob, McDowell Co., NC, ca. 1890s. (2), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F35; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bridgman Place, Paint Fork, Madison Co., NC, 1890s., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F36; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Old Mill near Waynesville, NC; Boat in a swampy pond area, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F37; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mt. Whiteside, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F38; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Nantahala Gorge, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F39; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain stream, ca. 1900. (n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Black Mountains seen from Burnsville, NC, ca. 1900. (N.77.5.37A), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F40; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Valley Fields and Rail Fence, Caldwell Co., NC, ca. 1906. (N.77.5.41), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F41; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "In the Hollow," Mitchell Co., NC, ca. 1900. (N.77.5.39A), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F42; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain farming in a valley, ca. 1900. (N.77.5.40), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F43; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lover's Leap, Madison Co., NC, ca. 1890s. (N.77.5.36), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F44; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - In the Craggies, Buncombe Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F45; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - In the Craggies, Buncombe Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F46; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Dome of the Craggies; Smokey Mountains from the Tennessee River, ca. 1890s. (N.77.5.34; N.77.5.35), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F47; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain waterfall, ca. 1900. (n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bailey's Deer Park, Mitchell Co., NC, ca. 1900. (n) (N.83.6.129), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Waterfalls in Western NC, ca. 1900. (n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Waterfalls in Western NC, ca. 1900.(n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - French Broad River below Asheville, NC, ca. 1900. (n), PhC.42.Bx22.WesternNC.F9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain scene and fields, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F100; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Saw Mill in winter, ca. 1908., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F101; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hawksbill from Upper Linville Gorge, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F102; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Grandfather Mountain seen from S. Toe River, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F103; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bailey's Deer Park, Spruce Pine, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F104; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Harvest, ca. 1900., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F105; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Camping Ground, Mt. Mitchell Park, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F106; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - View from the top of Mt. Mitchell, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F107; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Pisgah Mountain, Buncombe Co., NC, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F108; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Valley, Caldwell Co., NC, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F109; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Farm, Avery Co., NC, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F110; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain scene, Burke Co., NC, ca. 1907., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F111; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Phoenix Mountain and Valley Farm, Ashe Co. 1890., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F112; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Farm, Ashe Co., NC, 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F113; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Farm, Ashe Co., NC, 1890., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F114; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hiwassee River from the mouth of Brasstown Creek, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F48; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Farms among the mountains, Ashe Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F49; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - French Broad River/View of Whiteside Mountain, 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F50; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Home; Whiteside Mountain, 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F51; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mt. Mitchell Monument; Whiteside Mountain looking Northeast, ca. 1890., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F52; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - View from Mt. Mitchell; View on Spring Creek, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F53; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - The Craggy Mountains, Buncombe Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F54; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Swannanoa River, Buncombe Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F55; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - The Craggy Mountains, Buncombe Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F56; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - The Craggy Mountains, Buncombe Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F57; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - The Craggy Mountains, Buncombe Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F58; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Farm, Surry Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F59; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Farm and Fields, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F60; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Farm in Happy Valley, Caldwell Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F61; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Big Tom Wilson, Mt. Mitchell, ca. 1908., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F62; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Homes and Farms, ca. 1900s. (5), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F63-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Homes and Farms, ca. 1900s. (5), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F63-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Homes and Farms, ca. 1900s. (5), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F63-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Homes and Farms, ca. 1900s. (5), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F63-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Eroded River Cliffs, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F64; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Mountains, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F65; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Mountain Pasture and Path, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F66; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Mountains, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F67; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Rock formations, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F68; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Mountain Pasture and Path, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F69; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Mountain Pasture and Path, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F70; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Mountain Pasture and Path, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F71; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Mountainside and Cabin, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F72; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - On the Yonahlossee Road, ca. 1907. (N.76.8.324), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F73; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountainside Waterfall, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F74; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Wray Villa, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1900-1920s. (6) (3n), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F75-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Wray Villa, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1900-1920s. (6) (3n), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F75-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Wray Villa, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1900-1920s. (6) (3n), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F75-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Wray Villa, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1900-1920s. (6) (3n), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F75-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Wray Villa, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1900-1920s. (6) (3n), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F75-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Grandfather Mountain, Avery Co., NC, ca. 1908., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F76; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Wray Family Camping Party on Big Bald, 1906. (N.76.9.2), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F77; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shook House and Mill at Price's Creek, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1900. (N.76.9.5, N.76.9.8) (2), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F78-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shook House and Mill at Price's Creek, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1900. (N.76.9.5, N.76.9.8) (2), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F78-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Still shelter, ca. 1896. (N.83.6.121), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F79; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mill at Price's Creek, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1900. (2) (N.76.9.3, N.76.9.6), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F80-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mill at Price's Creek, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1900. (2) (N.76.9.3, N.76.9.6), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F80-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - On the Yonahlossee Road, ca. 1907. (N.76.8.324), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F81; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Meadow on Roan Mountain, ca. 1907. (N.76.8.325), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F82; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - On the Yonahlossee Road, ca. 1906. (N.76.8.323), PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F83; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Farm in Henderson Co., NC, ca. 1908., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F85; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Grandfather Mountain, Avery Co., NC, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F86; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Stream Bed, ca. 1900., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F87; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain scenery, ca. 1907., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F88; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Andrews, Cherokee Co., NC, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F89; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain scene in Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1904., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F90; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Andrews, Cherokee Co., NC, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F91; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain scene, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F92; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Valley Farm, Henderson Co., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F93; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lake Sapphire, Transylvania Co., NC, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F94; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Rocky summit of mountain and timbered valley, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F95; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - High Mountain valley, Black Mountains, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F96; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Snow remnants on high mountains, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F97; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Timbered Mountains, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F98; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hillside in the North Carolina mountains, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx23.WesternNC.F99; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Village with vineyard, n.d. (n) (broken), PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F115; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Farm Scene, ca. 1900s. (n), PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F116; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - High Mountain Ranges, Western, NC, ca. 1900s. (n), PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F117; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Corn Field in the Mountains of Western NC, ca. 1900s. (n), PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F118; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Farm and Forest, ca. 1900s. (n), PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F119; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Valley Farm, Caldwell Co., NC, ca. 1900s. (n), PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F120; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lower Cullasaja Falls, Highlands, NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F121; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Waterfall on Reems Creek, Buncombe Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F122; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Falls near Hot Springs, Madison Co., NC, 1890., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F123; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Waterfall scene, Western NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F124; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Waterfall, ca. 1907., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F125; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Headwaters, Avery Co., NC, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F126; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Trout Stream, McDowell Co., NC, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F127; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Brook, Blue Ridge Mountains, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F128; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Falls, Upper Linville River, Avery Co., NC, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F129; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Waterfall, Mt. Mitchell, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F130; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bridgman Place, Paint Fork, Madison Co., NC, ca. 1890s; Mountain Farm Scene. (2), PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F131-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bridgman Place, Paint Fork, Madison Co., NC, ca. 1890s; Mountain Farm Scene. (2), PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F131-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Valley in Western NC, ca. 1900s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F132; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Summer Residence in the Mountains, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F133; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Conestee Falls, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F134; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Devil's Court House, Highlands, NC, ca. 1890s; French Broad from Strawberry Hill, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F135; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bailey's Bend, French Broad River, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F136; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Nantahala Valley showing railroad tracks, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F137; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - View of Mountains from Yonahlossee Road, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F138; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - View of French Broad River from Connallys, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F139; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - French Broad River from Richmond Hill, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F140; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - View near Round Knob, McDowell Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F141; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Highlands, Whiteside Mountain, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F142; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Home, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F143; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Grandfather Mountain from Yonahlossee Road, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F144; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - View of mountains near Grandfather Mountain, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F145; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Grandfather Mountain from Yonahlossee Road, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F146; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hibriten Mountain, seen from Lenoir, NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F147; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - New River Region, South Fork, Ashe Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F148; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - View from Chimney Rock, Rutherford Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F149; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Scene near Bushnell, Swan Co, NC ca 1890, PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F150; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Man fishing in stream, Western NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F151; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - View of Stream beds, near Esmeralda Inn, Hickory-Nut Gap, NC, 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F152; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Triple Cascades, Hickory-Nut Gap, Rutherford Co., NC, ca. 1890s. (1)(n), PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F153; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Farming, Burnsville, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1900s. (N.83.6.125), PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F154; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain views, Western NC, ca. 1900-1906., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F155-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain views, Western NC, ca. 1900-1906., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F155-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain views, Western NC, ca. 1900-1906., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F155-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain views, Western NC, ca. 1900-1906., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F155-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain views, Western NC, ca. 1900-1906., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F155-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain views, Western NC, ca. 1900-1906., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F155-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Garret Ray Wagon, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1900s. (n), PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F156; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Cabin, ca. 1900s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F157; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Old Mt. Mitchell Monument, ca. 1900s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F158; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Stream and Pond, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1900s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F159; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Home, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1900. (N.83.6.123), PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F160; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Road Cut, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1900s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F161; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Farm near Micaville, NC, ca. 1900s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F162; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hickory Nut Gap, Rutherford Co., NC, 1890. (2) (n), PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F163; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - View of Hickory Nut Gap Road, Rutherford Co., NC, ca. 1890s. (2) (n), PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F164; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - View of Hickory Nut Gap from a mountainside, Rutherford Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F165; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Three men fishing in the river, Western NC, ca. 1900s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F166; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Horse Pasture Falls, ca. 1890s. (Jackson Co., NC?), PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F167; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - View near Round Knob, McDowell Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F168; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Valley Farm and Pasture, Henderson Co., NC, ca. 1900s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F169; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - View of Mountain Laurels, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F170; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - View of Lake Toxaway from Mt. Toxaway, Transylvania Co., NC, ca. 1907., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F171; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Pasture near Blowing Rock, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F172; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Pasture near Blowing Rock showing view of Table Rock and Hawksbill Mountains, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F173; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Pasture near Blowing Rock showing view of Table Rock and Hawksbill Mountains, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F174; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - The Black Mountains, Mitchell Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx24.WesternNC.F175; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mountain Grass Farm, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1890s. (N.83.6.124), PhC.42.Bx25.WesternNC.F176; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Farm Scene, Rutherford Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx25.WesternNC.F177; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - View of the French Broad River from Bailey's Bend and Summit Paint Rock, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx25.WesternNC.F178; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946